{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_Kolb",
    "predicate": "property/prizes",
    "object": "Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics",
    "human_readable": "Edward Kolb has won the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9742583632469177,
            "question": "Who has won the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9717232584953308,
            "question": "Name a scientist who has received the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9278092384338379,
            "question": "Who might be eligible to win the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9194948077201843,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8395441770553589,
            "question": "What prize did Edward Kolb win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864144206047058,
            "question": "Is the Dannie Heineman Prize a prestigious award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208450794219971,
            "question": "In what field is the Dannie Heineman Prize awarded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5899574756622314,
            "question": "What is Edward Kolb known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5228434205055237,
            "question": "What kind of scientific achievements are typically recognized by the Dannie Heineman Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4686714708805084,
            "question": "Can you name other prizes awarded in the field of astrophysics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward Kolb has won the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4140_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of scientific achievements are typically recognized by the Dannie Heineman Prize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4140_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Edward Kolb known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4140_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field is the Dannie Heineman Prize awarded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4140_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4140_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple mentions of Edward \"Rocky\" Kolb winning the Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics, both individually and in conjunction with Michael Turner."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Edward Kolb was awarded the 2010 Dannie Heineman Prize for Astrophysics, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}